<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>self-reflection on Jeremy Kao</title>
    <link>https://jeremykao.com/tags/self-reflection/</link>
    <description>Recent content in self-reflection on Jeremy Kao</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://jeremykao.com/tags/self-reflection/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Being Content</title>
      <link>https://jeremykao.com/posts/being-content/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Sep 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremykao.com/posts/being-content/</guid>
      <description>Recently, I was helping my friend assess what a good compensation package was for an early stage startup. My friend hadn&#39;t really had any startup experience, and I joined an early stage startup a few years back, so I guess I was qualified to judge how good the compensation package was. I said it was &amp;ldquo;pretty reasonable&amp;rdquo;, but my friend also talked to a few other folks. They all collectively said that it&#39;s &amp;ldquo;a bit low&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Goal Setting and Why it Ain&#39;t it</title>
      <link>https://jeremykao.com/posts/on-goal-setting/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Jun 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremykao.com/posts/on-goal-setting/</guid>
      <description>As with many folks who&#39;ve been stuck in the house for the past few months, I&#39;ve been a lot more attentive to my feelings. Deep down, I know I&#39;m dissatisfied with some things in my life, but it&#39;s been extremely difficult to pinpoint exactly what I need to change.
So I&#39;ve been analyzing and reflecting on my past, thinking about moments that brought me joy, specific events that made me anxious, specific annoyances at work, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Feeling I Can&#39;t Shake</title>
      <link>https://jeremykao.com/posts/a-feeling-i-cant-shake/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://jeremykao.com/posts/a-feeling-i-cant-shake/</guid>
      <description>I have almost everything anyone could ask for, but my emotions and mental state don&#39;t reflect that. Why?
 That&#39;s the question that&#39;s been killing me for the past couple of months.
The past few months have thrown me a ton of curveballs. I moved out of San Francisco and back into my parents place. On one hand, it&#39;s been awesome to chill with them and my sister. On the other hand, my days have become more and more routine.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>